Hui Wang

646-206-5709 | huiwang339@gmail.com | GitHub | Medium |

Full stack web developer with a passion for building applications that make our lives easier. Merging a background in health care with experience in Ruby on Rails and JavaScript based programming, I want to help enable companies to build apps take care of their customers in the best way possible.

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Parking App - Github: https://github.com/mypwhas9letters/parking-front | Demo

Rent out your driveway

Developed an app where users can list or rent a driveway.

Utilized Redux and React to develop a single page application to improve user experience.

Integrated Google's Maps and Calendar api to help organize reservations.

Created the backend using Rails and Postgres as a database.

Posigram- Github: https://github.com/mypwhas9letters/posigram | Demo

Photo sharing application where only positive comments are allowed

Used React to develop a single page photos sharing application.

Implemented a text analysis api to filter out comments with negative sentiment.

Included authorization and authentication to increase security.

$\textbf{Flatiron Mingle} - \underline{Github: https://github.com/mypwhas9letters/Flatiron-Mingle-FrontEnd} \mid \underline{Demo}$

Dating app

Created a dating app using vanilla Javascript.

Designed the questions form using HTML and CSS.

Allow the users to sort result of matches based on their preferences.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Ruby, Rails, SQL, Javascript, React, Redux, HTML, CSS

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Heart To Heart Home Care, Brooklyn, New York

Payroll, Billing, and Data Specialist, January 2015 - June 2017

Process weekly payroll for thousands of employees

Generate, submit, and correct electronic claims to insurance companies

Analyze data and create reports to evaluate company's performance

J&JC Beer Distribution, Elmhurst, New York

Data Entry, September 2012 - January 2015

Created invoices and maintained daily records of sales

Calculated commission for each sales representative according to each individual's performance

Supervised inventory control, coordinated deliveries, and communicated with suppliers

Radiation Safety Intern, Stony Brook, New York

Radiation Safety Intern, January 2012 - May 2012

Informed and comforted cancer patients undergoing radiation therapy

Audited laboratories and outpatient clinics for radiation contamination

Inspected lead vests and prepared rooms for radiation therapy

EDUCATION

Flatiron School - 2017

Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails and JavaScript program

Stony Brook University - Stony Brook, New York - May 2012

School of Health Technology and Management, Bachelor of Science in Health Science